Clint MooreTacoma, WAclint@ivy.ioQualifications summary:  Software Engineer with 10 years of experience covering many languagesand methodologies.  I find beauty in the details and continue toexpand my knowledge both professionally and in my own projects everyday.  Programming in Ruby, Python, Haskell, Erlang, and Common Lisp.I regularly use Postgres, MongoDB, Riak, Redis, Memcached, Couchbase,JSON, XML, REST-ful services, MVC, S3, EC2, and Dynamo.  Strong background in Systems Administration and Devops spanning almost20 years.  Experienced with maintaining and troubleshooting Linux, MacOS X, Solaris, FreeBSD, NetBSD, OpenBSD, OSF-1, Irix, Tru64, HP-UX,and AIX.Experience: NINJABLOCKS — 4/2012 - 6/2012- C programming on theArduino platform.- Connected Ruby on Rails to clustered Twitter, Facebook, Dropbox,  Instagram, Growl/Prowl, IMAP, Jabber/XMPP workers written in Haskell  with ZeroMQ.- Worked under tight deadlines due to kickstarter.com obligations.THOUGHTLEADR — 12/2011 - 4/2012Devops Engineer- Developed build and deployment automation in Python using Jenkins,  and Github.- Installed Nagios for monitoring, and Graphite for  visualization.- Maintained Celery distributed task queue, MongoDB, and Riak.- Coordinated with development team to asses current and future  scaling requirements.TECHNOLOFT, LLC — 2/2010 -10/2011- Delivered a Mac OS X Cocoa application written in Haskell.- Provided technical sales support.- Coordinated with customer business unit to define goals and requirements.WHITEPAGES.COM — 9/2009 -1/2010- Maintenance and support of Ruby on Rails site.- Troubleshot HTML, CSS, and Javascript issues.- Coordinated with QA team to ensure complete issue resolution.DOUBLE PRIME — 5/2009 - 10/2009- Maintenance and support of mod_perl web site.- Coordinated with customer QA team.- Provided professional communication of technical issues to business team.BLUE BOX GROUP, LLC — 3/2007 - 4/2009-Wrote internal billing and provisioning software in Ruby on Rails, using HTMLDOC, MySQL, Authorize.net, JSON.- Developed automatic site scaling technology using Erlang, ZeroMQ,- Ruby on Rails, and Virtuozzo.- Systems and Network administrator with Barracuda, Nginx, MySQL,  Postini, Passenger, Apache.CRYPTONETS, LLC — 5/2006 - 2/2007- Designed and implemented real estate web site with Ruby on Rails.- Built realtime and event-driven data collectors in Erlang for  Multiple Listings Service.- Worked with customer to define project requirements.AMAZON.COM — 3/2005 - 4/2006- Maintained Perl, Mason subsite of Amazon.com.- Coordinated with QA team to confirm correct issue resolution.- Worked with team using Agile development.INTEGRATED CONCRETE SYSTEMS — 6/2002 - 1/2005- Built automated dispatching software using Ruby on Rails, Perl, and Erlang.- Developed J2ME application for Nextel phones.- Provided succinct and approachable explanations of technical details  to business departments.CENTRAL DESIGN SYSTEMS — 6/2001 - 5/2002- Delivered, configured, and troubleshot Sun, Veritas, Cisco, F5, and  Checkpoint hardware and software.- Coordinated with customer teams to resolve issues.SAPIENT HEALTH NETWORK — 1/1998 - 5/2001- Solaris systems administration concerned with Sendmail, Apache,  LDAP, NFS, NIS, YP, and Bind.SPIRE TECHNOLOGY — 1996 - 1997- Linux and Solaris systems administration with Sendmail, inn, Apache,  and Radius.- Network administration with Cisco, Livingston, and Adtran.TRANSPORT LOGIC — 1996 - 1994- Linux and FreeBSD systems administration.- inn, NCSA httpd, Sendmail, NFS, and RADIUS.- Coordinated with technical support staff to resolve customer issues.